MakerDAO is now Sky — the next evolution of DeFi. Explore [Sky.money](https://sky.money/) and get rewarded for saving without giving up control.

Developers

Learn

Foundation

Developers

Learn

Foundation

Community

Menu

Privacy Policy
==============

Last Updated: 10 September 2018

This Privacy Policy provides our privacy policy regarding the nature, purpose, use, and sharing of personal data or other information collected from the users of the website makerdao.com and other websites which use subdomains of makerdao.com (the „Site”). We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. Please read this carefully as this Privacy Policy is legally binding when you use the Site.

As used in this Privacy Policy, "we", "us" or "our" refers to Maker Ecosystem Growth Holdings, Inc., a Cayman based limited liability company. You can reach us with any request relating to this Privacy Policy via contact details provided below.

[](#data-processing-in-connection-with-the-site)Data processing in connection with the Site
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

### [](#use-of-cookies-and-similar-technologies)Use of Cookies and Similar Technologies

The Site is using cookies. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. Cookies are typically stored on your computer's hard drive. Information collected from cookies is used by us to evaluate the effectiveness of our Site and analyze trends. The information collected from cookies allows us to determine such things as which parts of the Site are most visited and difficulties our visitors may experience in accessing the SIte. With this knowledge, we can improve the quality of your experience on the Site by recognizing and delivering more of the most desired features and information, as well as by resolving access difficulties.

We use third party service providers, to assist us in better understanding the use of our Site. Our service providers will place cookies on the hard drive of your computer (or use similar technologies) and will receive information that we select that will educate us on such things as how visitors navigate around our Site. This information is aggregated to provide statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not personally identify individuals. This information may include:

* Computer or mobile device information,
* Website usage information, such as:
    
    * Page views,
    * Button clicks,
    * Input form changes (without the values being entered),
    * Errors.

Our service providers analyses this information and provides us with aggregate reports. The information and analysis provided by our service providers will be used to assist us in better understanding our visitors' interests in our Site and how to better serve those interests. If you want to avoid using cookies altogether, you can disable cookies in your browser. However, disabling cookies might make it impossible for you to use certain features of the Site. Your use of the Site with a browser that is configure to accept cookies constitutes an acceptance of our and third-party cookies.

### [](#email-marketing)Email Marketing

If you subscribe to our newsletter we may occasionally communicate project news, updates, promotions and related information relating to MakerDAO. We shall only do this where you have given us your consent. If you want to opt out of receiving promotional and marketing emails in relation to which you might receive in accordance with this section, you can best opt out by clicking "unsubscribe" at the bottom of an email we sent you.

### [](#your-inquiries)Your inquiries

You may contact us by e-mail to the following e-mail address: [\[email protected\]](https://makerdao.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). We use the data that you provide in an email to us, which you may give voluntarily, only in order to answer your contact question or to reply to your email in the best possible manner.

### [](#social-media)Social media

We may use plugins from social networks such as GitHub, YouTube, Reddit, Twitter, Telegram, Medium on the Site. When you activate them (by clicking on them), the operators of the respective social networks may record that you are on the Site and may use this information. This processing of your personal data lays in the responsibility of these individual social media platforms and occurs according to their privacy policies. Please check with these individual social media platforms regarding their privacy policies. We are not responsible for data collected by these individual social media platforms.

[](#your-rights)Your rights
---------------------------

### [](#right-to-access)Right to access

As a data subject you have the right to obtain from us free information about your personal data processed at any time and a copy of this information. Furthermore, you will have access to the following information: the purposes of the processing; the categories of personal data concerned; where possible, the envisaged period for which the personal data will be processed, or, if not possible, the criteria used to determine that period; the existence of the right to request from us rectification or erasure of personal data, or restriction of processing of personal data concerning you, or to object to such processing; the existence of the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority; where the personal data are not collected directly from you, any available information as to their source; and the existence of automated decision-making, including profiling, and, at least in those cases, meaningful information about the logic involved, as well as the significance and envisaged consequences of such processing for you.

### [](#right-to-rectification)Right to rectification

You have the right to obtain from us, without undue delay, the rectification of inaccurate personal data concerning you. Taking into account the purposes of the processing, you shall have the right to have incomplete personal data completed, including by means of providing a supplementary statement.

### [](#right-to-be-forgotten)Right to be forgotten

You have the right to obtain from us the erasure of personal data concerning you as soon as possible, and we shall have the obligation to erase personal data without undue delay where required by the law, including when:

* the personal data is no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which they were collected or otherwise processed;
* there is no longer a legal ground for the processing;
* you object to the processing and there are no overriding legitimate grounds for the processing;
* the personal data has been unlawfully processed;
* the personal data must be erased for compliance with a legal obligation in accordance with the applicable law to which we are subject.

### [](#right-to-restriction-of-processing)Right to restriction of processing

You have the right to obtain from the Foundation restriction of processing where one of the following applies:

* the accuracy of the personal data is contested by you, for a period enabling us to verify the accuracy of the personal data;
* the processing is unlawful and you oppose the erasure of the personal data and requests instead the restriction of their use instead;
* we no longer needs the personal data for the purposes of the processing, but they are required by you for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims; and/o
* you have objected to processing pursuant to applicable laws.

### [](#right-to-object)Right to object

You have the right to object, on grounds relating to your particular situation, at any time, to the processing of personal data concerning you. We shall no longer process the personal data in the event of the objection, unless we can demonstrate reasonable grounds for the processing, which override the interests, rights and freedoms of you, or for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims.

### [](#right-to-withdraw-data-protection-consent)Right to withdraw data protection consent

You have the right to withdraw your consent to processing of your personal data at any time.

[](#international-transfers)International transfers
---------------------------------------------------

We are entitled to transfer your personal data to third parties abroad for the purposes of the data processing.

As personal data processors, they are obliged to protect data privacy to the same extent as we ourselves. We choose the processors carefully to ensure compliance with applicable laws.

[](#data-security)Data security
-------------------------------

We use appropriate technical and organizational security measures to protect your personal data. Our security measures are continuously being improved in line with technical developments.

Please note that any data transmission on the Internet (e.g. communication by e-mail) is generally not secure and we accept no liability for data transmitted to us via the Internet. Unfortunately, absolute protection is not technically possible. This information does not apply to the websites of third parties and the corresponding links given on the Site. We assume no responsibility and liability for these.

[](#duration-of-data-processing)Duration of data processing
-----------------------------------------------------------

We will process your personal data only for the period necessary to achieve the purpose of the processing, or as required by applicable laws. After the period the personal data will be deleted.

[](#amendments-to-this-policy)Amendments to this Policy
-------------------------------------------------------

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended version on the Site including the effective date of the amended version. The current version of the Privacy Policy, as published on the Site, is applicable.

[](#contact)Contact
-------------------

Please contact us with questions, comments, or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy as well as with any requests at [\[email protected\]](https://makerdao.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

By using our site you agree to our [Cookie Policy](https://makerdao.com/en/privacy/#use-of-cookies-and-similar-technologies).

Resources

Products

Developers

Foundation

English

* Dansk
    
* Español
    
* Italiano
    
* 日本語
    
* 한국어
    
* Português (Brasil)
    
* Pусский
    
* 中文 (简体)
